[
    {
        "front": "George Washington was the first president",
        "back": "George Washington"
    },
    {
        "front": "John Adams was the second president",
        "back": "John Adams"
    },
    {
        "front": "John Elway played for the denver broncos",
        "back": "John Elway"
    },
    {
        "front": "James Comey was the FBI director that was fired by Donald Trump",
        "back": "James Comey"
    },
    {
        "front": "Founded in 1607, Jamestown was considered to be the first english settlement in the new world",
        "back": "Jamestown"
    },
    {
        "front": "Formerly known as Bedloe's Island, Liberty Island is the current name of the island where the Statue of Liberty is located",
        "back": "Bedloe's Island"
    },
    {
        "front": "Glacier National Park is located in the Northwest corner of Montana and has the nickname 'Crown of the Continent'",
        "back": "Glacier National Park"
    },
    {
        "front": "Donald Trump is the oldest person to be elected to the office of President of the United States",
        "back": "Donald Trump"
    },
    {
        "front": "The Statue of Liberty holds a torch in her right hand",
        "back": "torch"
    },
    {
        "front": "Pony Express is the name of the US Mail service started in 1860 that used horses and riders",
        "back": "Pony Express"
    }
]